- I'm sorry?
- Well, last time you bought a new shirt...
(Penny:)...was when we were dating.
So, what we did was in fact dating?
(Penny:)Well, yeah, we did have a date.
(Leonard:)Exactly. Thank you.
Do me a favor, tell Koothrappali that
next time you see him.
(Penny:)So who is she?
- Oh, she's a doctor.
- Oh, nice.
A "doctor" doctor,
or a you kind of doctor?
"Doctor" doctor. Surgical resident.
(Leonard:)Smart, pretty.
(Leonard:)Let me ask you something.
(Leonard:)If your friend thinks
he's dating someone...
(Leonard:)...but he's not, because in fact,
you're dating her...
(Leonard:)...does that make you a bad person?
- Well, that depends.
- On what?
(Penny:)Is that friend Wolowitz?
(Penny:)- Yeah.
- Screw him, you're fine.
- Are you sure?
- Well, have you slept with her yet?